going to run a tiny house off of this
one walrus and it's so easy to put in it
is on Wheels oh my God all we're going
to do is this separate the circuits that
we want to control from this panel and
put it in a sub panel right here then
we're going to take a breaker and run it
down to this plug and then off of the
sub panel we're going to take another
breaker and run it to this plug take
this wall right here hit this button
take this and plug it in here
and then plug it in there and then going
to take our solar leads and plug them in
here you literally just plug it in and
dude the coolest thing is you don't even
have to put solar panels on this thing
bro you can set it to charge during off
peak hours when energy is 9 cents a
kilowatt hour and then set it to
discharge during peak hours when it's 55
cents a kilowatt hour St un power yes
and it's also a backup generator and
guess what there's also a 30% solar tax
credit on it right now and many states
have their own state tax credit like
South Carolina 25% off too you can
literally get this in South Carolina for
55% off right
now want one cheap I got you baby I'm
I'm with
it let's go ncol I would be proud of
wson Wang and I hope Joe fails